hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is jar
mikowski this week got a little bit of a
throat thing going on but decided I'm
still going to be able to record this I
want to talk about if you're a coach
Mentor or trainer or you just want to
get into the industry how do you turn
your knowledge into a group coaching
program that's marketable tangible that
people are going to actually buy from
you what are those first steps now I've
always broken this down for people very
simply into about six steps they want to
start with
so the six steps look like this number
one you got to know what your Niche is
and I and I would say if you're watching
this I hope that you have your Niche
figured out it's not super difficult to
figure out what your Niche is the reason
why most people don't have it figured
out is because they're afraid of picking
the wrong one or they're afraid of
missing out on Opportunity by picking
something that's not going to be the
right thing for them when in fact it's
actually very simple most of us have an
idea for the niche that we want to pick
sometimes we have two or three that we
could combine together and then use
those now the stage that you want to
focus on is you want to actually build
out something that people want and this
is what I coach my clients in in the
wealthy coach Academy program I'm going
to give you a bird's eyee view as to how
I would get started if I was you if you
were starting your own group coaching
program before we go on to that though I
want to mention that a group coaching
program the reason why we like group
coaching is because it leverages your
time for the money that you can make
one-on-one coaching you're trading
dollars for hours with group coaching
you get to show up once people pay you a
monthly fee or they pay you one time and
you can mentor those people and it's an
incredible way to leverage your efforts
into being profitable profitability is
the name of that game right there as
well as the impact that you can have on
people and so I want you to think about
what is the number one thing that I know
and have experience in I can help people
with for me it's generating leads and
growing coaching businesses I've been
doing that for 22 years and that's what
I know how to help people with I know
how to get you to seven and even eight
figures in your business even if you're
just starting out from zero maybe you're
like I don't want to make that much
that's a lot of money Jeremiah I can't
even think about that or imagine that I
know how to get you the first $ 10,000
$220,000 a month and hopefully I mean
that's a great goal for you if your
group coaching program was paying you
$10 to $20,000 per month while only
working 5 to 10 hours a week mentoring
people uh that's a game Cher okay so I
want you to think about what you do what
you know how to do what you're good at
and we got to package that into
something that people actually want okay
and so what I'm going to do here is I'm
actually going to use an example uh from
a conversation that I had earlier today
with somebody and I'm going to use this
to brainstorm some
ideas which is awesome so I use a tool
with AI called po po.com is my favorite
AI tool because it combines a number of
different AI tools like GPT deep seek
Gemini uh Claude 35 but there's also
Cloud 37 so these are different AI
algorithms and I like to use multiple
AIS to be able to get to our answer one
of the best ones that's out there is GPT
4.5 preview good all around is GPT 40 uh
as well as uh the 03 mini models okay so
those are great and what we're going to
do we're going to use for the sake of
this example gbt 40 which is the same AI
model that the free version of chat gbt
uses which is awesome and so because of
that I mean it's it's a very lowcost
inexpensive AI model that you can use
that does a lot of great things has a
lot of potential to it so what we're
going to do is I'm going to use an
example and say I want to make a
coaching program around dog
grooming I've built
successful dog
grooming
business to multiple six figures I want
to help others who want to get into the
business okay and so you could translate
that to any Niche that you want to do
generate for me 10 ideas for how my
program itself as an online community
support and courses might look give
examples okay and so the AI is going to
go to work and come up with 10 different
examples of what this might look like uh
structured online course with
step-by-step modules private Facebook
group weekly coaching calls
certification program templates and
scripts maybe some one-on-one coaching
options you don't necessarily need that
grooming techniques Library can you
don't need all all that accountability
program with Milestones guest experts
done with you launch package now what I
like is I like most of these as far as
like let's say certification program
live coaching call uh a Facebook group
or Discord Community or a school
Community a lot of people are using
platform called school.com to build
stuff out it's right here
okay as well as uh yeah having a course
of some kind Okay so
generate for me 10 ideas for my first
course in this program okay here are 10
ideas for your course dog rooming
business Basics from Passion to profit
mastering the fundamentals how to build
a business plan first 10
clients uh sixf figure dog Grom is blint
and I like I like these two right here
six figureure dog gromer blue blueprint
and your first 10 clients cuz it kind of
focuses on those two things uh um of
building a business and then doing it
that way so again the AI can help you
brainstorm a lot of this and come up
with a lot of this right here now what I
like to do is I like to toss around and
I have some free chat gbt prompts that
I've actually put together it's over at
my website over at Jeremiah Kowski tocom
you can go check it out right here at
the top of the site free AI prompts
these are chat GPT prompts you can use
them for any other AI but they're really
great at coming up with sales copy as
well as marketing ideas so our Master
marketing ideas
prompt let's say we're going to run
with this idea right
here and then I'm going to tell it I'm
going to copy this master
prompt right
here it's going to come up with ideas
for what this might look like coaching
program overw the dog RoR success
accelerator $1,000 help aspiring 8 weeks
long live in sessions self-based
[Music]
modules so this gives you an idea as far
as what deliverables that you're going
to be delivering to people but now this
is where it gets really fun is you can
start to have it develop out for
you landing page copy and this is where
it starts to get realistic and tangible
and you start to see the results
firsthand that you're hoping to
experience ready to start your dog
rooming business join my free webinar
turn your passion for dogs into a
profitable business you ever dreamed of
building a career around your love for
dogs maybe you thought about
business so this is really kind of like
very vanilla and kind of lame for what
we would say so that's why we want to go
through these different steps of prompts
here and see what kind of copy it can
generate and this is the stage right
here you might be saying okay Jeremiah I
want to know like what how do I get
started this is the stage where I would
start everybody at as I would have you
play around with AI literally you pick
your Niche let's go hit the AI now and
let's come up with ideas for how do we
describe it what's the pain points
what's the customer I want to get into
the mind of your prospect I want to
understand them so before we build
anything out before we create anything
we're going to get into the mindset of
what we're actually offering and
understanding so that's what these
promps help us
do uh let's see pain points they wor
they'll be stuck in a job they
they don't
love they're unsure on how to start they
feel overwhelmed they're worried they're
going to be wasting their time and money
on mistakes they're struggling to find
clients
okay they feel lost and confused as to
where to start a business struggling to
research with the
plan their own di mindset see to th th
your business tired of feeling stuck
struggling to find clients want to start
dog business stop dreaming and start
doing three step system to build a
thriving dog grooming business starting
today so again I like that as far as the
headline
goes for our sales
copy and now it's going to start to
write us some copy right here Love Dogs
ready to start your own groomy business
but don't know where to start imagine
working with dogs in your
day there you go and sorry excuse me for
the yawning it's a little it's a little
late here but
okay this next prompt is called The
Epiphany Bridge prompt and this really
cranks it up to level 500 helps us
understand where somebody is coming from
they spent hours Googling watching
YouTube videos reading every article
because that's real that's what people
end up doing and that's what you want is
you want your sales copy ideas to be
real and to mirror what real human
behavior is
like I'm going to skip ahead here
there's a couple of other steps but I
want to skip to this last one right here
step six story selling framework
storytelling
framework we're going to paste this one
right here and it's going to generate us
some sales copy for a landing page based
on those new ideas are you tired of
feeling unstuck and unsure about how to
start your own business I get it I know
exactly what it's like dreaming of
working with dogs and well this is how
it came out are you tired of feeling
stuck andure how to start your dog
groming business I get it I know exactly
where you are with the dream building
something on your own finally leaving
your behind an unfulfilling job what
when you start your own business no I
was terrified too I didn't know where to
begin I didn't have clients and so right
here the AI is able to write for us some
of the sales copy right here if you take
this even a step further it just keeps
going on and on and on doing that now
when it comes to building this as your
own business creating a landing page
yourself on your own website is going to
be your next steps Gathering as many
people around you and being able to get
people to join your community your
audience of people to become your client
those are the first steps that you want
to take when you're transitioning from
any sort of environment uh field group
of people that's doing this into a group
mentoring program and then from here you
have your program that you can start to
Market you can start to get your first
clients and that becomes the kind of
income that you want to generate stay
tuned follow this page right here and
we'll give you more techniques and
strategies on how to use technique uh
technology to grow your own business
online talk soon
[Music]
[Applause]